Guide to the Penn State Extension records 01131
Eberly Family Special Collections Library
- 01: County Reports, 1
  - Washington County
    - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, 1916-1930; cuid1418; 1 Items (Box 167)
    - Extension Reports, 1945-1952; cuid1419 (Box 182)
    - 4-H newspaper clippings, 1969; cuid1420 (Box 182)
    - 4-H newspaper clippings, 1952-1956; cuid1421 (Box 182)
    - Gold Medal Colt Club Roundup, 1939; cuid1422 (Box 182)
    - Historical Sketch, undated; cuid1423 (Box 182)
    - Home Economics Narrative Summary, 1925-1962; cuid1424; 1 Items (Box 167)
    - Home Economics newspaper clippings, 1963-1964; cuid1425 (Box 182)
    - Horse and Pony newspaper clippings, 1963-1964; cuid1426 (Box 182)
    - In Penn's Woods Bulletin 31, 1923/05; cuid1427 (Box 182)
    - Meeting, Annual, 1933-1964; cuid1429 (Box 183)
    - Meeting, Annual Programs, 1938-1960; cuid1430 (Box 182)
    - Meeting Minutes and Reports, 1912-1964; cuid1428 (Box 182)
    - Members Listing, 1915-1960; cuid1431 (Box 183)
    - Mollenauer, Elizabeth notebook, 1948-1960; cuid1432 (Box 182)
    - Monthly and Program Reports, 1965-1966; cuid1433 (Box 182)
    - Narrative Report, Annual, 1963-1966; cuid1434 (Box 183)
    - Newsletter, 1946; cuid1435 (Box 182)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1960-1964; cuid1436 (Box 182)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1968-1969; cuid1438 (Box 182)
    - Pennsylvania Livestock Field Day Program, 1951/06/18; cuid1439 (Box 183)
    - Press Clippings, undated; cuid1440; 1 Items (Box 168)
    - Senior Extension Club Meeting Minutes Book, 1946-1959; cuid1441 (Box 182)
    - Sesquicentennial Publicity newspaper clippings, 1960; cuid1442 (Box 182)
    - State Supplementary Reports, 1923-1953; cuid1443; 3 Items (Box 167)
    - State Supplementary Reports, 1954-1962; cuid1444; 8 Items (Box 168)
    - Statistical Report, Annual, 1963-1967; cuid1445 (Box 182)
    - Supplementary Report, 1963-1966; cuid1446 (Box 183)
    - Town and Country newspaper clippings, 1963-1964; cuid1447 (Box 182)
    - Treasurer's Report, 1950-1957; cuid1448 (Box 183)
    - Triennial Farm Census, 1924; cuid1449 (Box 182)
    - Work Plan, 1962-1970; cuid1450 (Box 183)
    - Yocum vs Board of Directors, 2000 (Box 280)
  - Wayne County
    - Agent Reports, 1919-1950; cuid1451; 1 Items (Box 98)
    - Agent Reports, 1951-1985; cuid1452; 1 Items (Box 99)
    - Anniversary, 25th and 50th, 1919-1969; cuid1454; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 2000 (Box 278)
    - Annual Report, 2002 (Box 277)
    - Annual Report, 2007 (Box 277)
    - Annual Reports, 1990-1991; cuid1455; 1 Items (Box 173)
  - Westmoreland County
    - A-100, 1995; cuid1482 (Box 195)
    - Agent Reports, 1915-1950; cuid1483; 1 Items (Box 97)
    - Agent Reports, 1951-1973; cuid1484; 1 Items (Box 98)
    - Agent Reports, 1974-1977; cuid1486; 1 Items (Box 101)
    - Agent Reports, 1979-1980; cuid1487; 1 Items (Box 101)
    - Anniversary, Golden, 1915-1965; cuid1488; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Reports, 1916-1919; cuid1496 (Box 189)
    - Annual Report, 1918; cuid1489; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Reports, 1920-1923; cuid1497 (Box 188)
    - Annual Reports, 1924; cuid1492 (Box 188)
    - Annual Reports, 1925-1927; cuid1498 (Box 188)
    - Annual Reports, 1928; cuid1493 (Box 189)
    - Annual Reports, 1929; cuid1494 (Box 188)
    - Annual Reports, 1930; cuid1495 (Box 188)
    - Annual Reports, 1931-1939; cuid1499 (Box 189)
    - Annual Reports, 1940-1943; cuid1500 (Box 188)
    - Annual Reports, 1945-1947; cuid1501 (Box 188)
    - Annual Report, 1963-1964; cuid1491 (Box 187)
    - Annual Reports, 1968-1969; cuid1502 (Box 189)
    - Annual Report, 1977; cuid1490; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Reports, 1988-1991; cuid1503; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Annual Reports, 1996-1997; cuid1504; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 2002 (Box 278)
    - Annual Report, 2003-2004 (Box 278)
    - Annual Reports: Enrollment, 1970-1982; cuid1505 (Box 185)
    - Annual Reports: Enrollment, 1983-1993; cuid1506 (Box 186)
    - Clover Counter, 1991/01; cuid1507 (Box 194)
    - Executive Committee Notebook, 1916-1945; cuid1508 (Box 189)
    - Extension Association Annual Meeting Minutes and Treasurers Reports, 1933-1950; cuid1509 (Box 190)
    - 4-H EFNEP Enrollment, 1986-1987; cuid1457 (Box 190)
    - 4-H EFNEP Enrollment, 1987; cuid1456 (Box 196)
    - 4-H EFNEP Enrollment, 1988-1989; cuid1458 (Box 195)
    - 4-H Enrollment, 1974-1976; cuid1470 (Box 195)
    - 4-H Enrollment, 1977-1978; cuid1471 (Box 190)
    - 4-H Enrollment, 1980-1983; cuid1472 (Box 193)
    - 4-H Enrollment, 1985-1987; cuid1473 (Box 190)
    - 4-H Enrollment, 1979; cuid1459 (Box 195)
    - 4-H Enrollment, 1983; cuid1460 (Box 193)
    - 4-H Enrollment, 1984; cuid1461 (Box 195)
    - 4-H Enrollment, 1987; cuid1462 (Box 196)
    - 4-H Enrollment, 1988; cuid1463 (Box 195)
    - 4-H Enrollment, 1989; cuid1464 (Box 193)
    - 4-H Enrollment, 1990; cuid1465 (Box 193)
    - 4-H Enrollment, 1992; cuid1466 (Box 193)
    - 4-H Enrollment, 1992-1993; cuid1474 (Box 194)
    - 4-H Enrollment, 1994; cuid1467 (Box 193)
    - 4-H Enrollment, 1995; cuid1468 (Box 194)
    - 4-H Enrollment, 1997; cuid1469 (Box 193)
    - 4-H Enrollment, 1997-1999; cuid1475 (Box 194)
    - 4-H School Enrollment, 1986-1988; cuid1476 (Box 190)
    - 4-H School Enrollment, 1986-1988; cuid1477 (Box 196)
    - 4-H School Enrollment, 1989-1990; cuid1478 (Box 195)
    - 4-H School Enrollment, 1990-1993; cuid1479 (Box 193)
    - 4-H School Enrollment, 1993-1996; cuid1480 (Box 195)
    - 4-H School Enrollment, 1994-1997; cuid1481 (Box 194)
    - School Enrollment, 1997-1998; cuid1510 (Box 193)
  - Wyoming County
    - Agent Reports, 1917-1965; cuid1511; 1 Items (Box 100)
    - Agent Reports, 1972-1983; cuid1513; 1 Items (Box 101)
    - Agent Reports, 1985; cuid1514; 1 Items (Box 101)
    - Annual Reports, 1989-1991; cuid1515; 1 Items (Box 173)
    - Annual Report, 2000 (Box 278)
    - Annual Report, 2007 (Box 278)
  - Wysox County
    - Agent Reports, 1980-1983; cuid1516; 1 Items (Box 103)
  - York County
    - Agent Reports, 1967; cuid1517; 1 Items (Box 102)
    - Agent Reports, 1917-1935; cuid1518; 1 Items (Box 101)
    - Agent Reports, 1936-1965; cuid1519; 1 Items (Box 102)
    - Agent Reports, 1968-1983; cuid1520; 1 Items (Box 103)
    - Anniversary, 50th, 1917-1967; cuid1521; 1 Items (Box 174)
    - Annual Report, 2001 (Box 277)
    - Annual Report, 2007 (Box 277)
    - Annual Report, 2009 (Box 277)
    - Annual Report, 2010 (Box 278)
    - Annual Report, 2011 (Box 278)
    - Correspondence, 2010-2011; cuid1522 (Box 238)
    - 4-H Club Charter Application, 1965 (Box 280)
- 02: Correspondence Course Study, 1
  - 01: Course Lessons, 1
    - Clovers and Grasses, undated; cuid1523; 1 Items (Box 225, Folder 3)
    - Commercial Fertilizers, undated; cuid1524; 1 Items (Box 225, Folder 4)
    - Dairy Breeds of Cattle, undated; cuid1525; 1 Items (Box 225, Folder 5)
    - Dressing and Curing Meats, undated; cuid1526; 1 Items (Box 225, Folder 6)
    - Dual Purpose Breeds of Cattle, undated; cuid1527; 1 Items (Box 225, Folder 7)
    - Farm Bookkeeping, undated; cuid1528; 1 Items (Box 225, Folder 8)
    - Farm Manure, undated; cuid1529; 1 Items (Box 225, Folder 9)
    - Grain Crops, undated; cuid1530; 1 Items (Box 225, Folder 10)
    - Principles of Breeding, undated; cuid1531; 1 Items (Box 225, Folder 11)
    - Principles of Fruit Growing, undated; cuid1532; 1 Items (Box 225, Folder 12)
    - Silo and Ensilage Crops, undated; cuid1533; 1 Items (Box 225, Folder 13)
    - Swine Husbandry, undated; cuid1534; 1 Items (Box 225, Folder 14)
    - Tile Draining, undated; cuid1535; 1 Items (Box 225, Folder 15)
    - Tubers and Roots, undated; cuid1536; 1 Items (Box 225, Folder 16)
    - Vegetable Gardening, undated; cuid1537; 1 Items (Box 225, Folder 17)
  - 02: Student Inquiries, 2
    - A-F, 1896/12; cuid1538; 1 Items (Box 223, Folder 23)
    - A-Z, 1893; cuid1539; 1 Items (Box 223, Folder 04-06)
    - A-Z, 1892/05-11; cuid1540; 1 Items (Box 223, Folder 01-03)
    - A-Z, 1894/01-10; cuid1541; 1 Items (Box 223, Folder 07-10)
    - A-Z, 1894/10-1895/01; cuid1542; 1 Items (Box 223, Folder 11-13)
    - A-Z, 1895/01-12; cuid1543; 1 Items (Box 223, Folder 14-16)
    - A-Z, 1896/08-11; cuid1544; 1 Items (Box 223, Folder 17-19)
    - A-Z, 1896/11-12; cuid1545; 1 Items (Box 223, Folder 20-22)
    - A-Z, 1897/01; cuid1546; 1 Items (Box 224, Folder 04-06)
    - A-Z, 1897/02; cuid1547; 1 Items (Box 224, Folder 07-09)
    - A-Z, 1897/03-10; cuid1548; 1 Items (Box 224, Folder 10-12)
    - A-Z, 1897/10-11; cuid1549; 1 Items (Box 224, Folder 13-15)
    - A-Z, 1897/11-12; cuid1550; 1 Items (Box 224, Folder 16-18)
    - A-Z, 1897/12; cuid1551; 1 Items (Box 224, Folder 19-21)
    - G-Z, 1896/12; cuid1552; 1 Items (Box 224, Folder 01-03)
    - H-Z, 1898/03-09; cuid1553; 1 Items (Box 224, Folder 22)
    - H-Z, 1898/03-09; cuid1554; 1 Items (Box 225, Folder 01-02)
    - Student records, 1901-1904 (Box 227)
    - Student records, 1899-1900 (Box 228)
    - Student records, 1904-1905 (Box 230)
    - Student records, 1906-1908 (Box 231)
    - Student records - Chautaugua course, 1897-1901 (Box 229)
- 03: Short Course Study, 2
  - 01: Course Inquiries
    - Creamery Course A-F, 1897/01-04; cuid1555; 1 Items (Box 225, Folder 21)
    - Creamery Course A-G, 1896/11-12; cuid1556; 1 Items (Box 225, Folder 18)
    - Creamery Course G-M, 1897/01-04; cuid1557; 1 Items (Box 225, Folder 22)
    - Creamery Course H-M, 1896/11-12; cuid1558; 1 Items (Box 225, Folder 19)
    - Creamery Course N-Z, 1896/11-12; cuid1559; 1 Items (Box 225, Folder 20)
    - Creamery Course N-Z, 1897/01-04; cuid1560; 1 Items (Box 225, Folder 23)
- 04: General Course Administration Records, 3
  - 01: Correspondence Regarding Receipt and Grading of Lessons
    - A-Z, 1900/10-12; cuid1561; 1 Items (Box 226, Folder 07-08)
    - A-Z, 1901/01/12; cuid1562; 1 Items (Box 226, Folder 09-10)
    - A-Z, 1901/03-04; cuid1563; 1 Items (Box 226, Folder 11-12)
  - 02: Financial Records
    - A-W, 1895/04-12; cuid1564; 1 Items (Box 226, Folder 03-04)
    - A-Z, 1892/05-1894/04; cuid1565; 1 Items (Box 226, Folder 01-02)
    - A-Z, 1896/01-12; cuid1566; 1 Items (Box 226, Folder 05-06)
  - 03: Journals
    - Agricultural Correspondence Courses Enrollment, 1946-1982; cuid1572; 1 Items (Box 232)
    - Record of Lessons in Correspondence Study, 1904-1905; cuid1567; 1 Items
    - Record of Students Taking Lessons in Chautauqua Course, 1897-1901; cuid1568; 1 Items
    - Student Records, 1901-1904; cuid1569; 1 Items
    - Student Records, 1906-1908; cuid1570; 1 Items
    - Untitled Pages, 1899-1900; cuid1571; 1 Items
- 05: 4-H, 4
  - 100 Years of 4-H, 2002, September 29; cuid1573 (Box 191)
  - Agriculture and 4-H buttons, undated (Box 283)
  - Annual 4-H Youth Enrollment Reports SE Region, 2002-2006; cuid1696 (Box 235)
  - Calcium-Rich Cookery 4-H Series - Lessons 1-4, undated; cuid1653; 1 Items (Box 177)
  - Centennial correspondence, 2012 (Box 283)
  - Centennial stickers, 2012 (Box 283)
  - County Agent, 1978; cuid1654; 1 Items (Box 191)
  - County Agent, 1983; cuid1655; 1 Items (Box 191)
  - County Agent, 1997; cuid1656; 1 Items (Box 191)
  - County Agent, 1999; cuid1657; 1 Items (Box 191)
  - Discussion Guides for Teachers and Leaders - 4-H TV Action Club Program, undated; cuid1658; 1 Items (Box 179)
  - Eating Right is Basic 2 for 4-H, undated; cuid1659; 1 Items; Textual--Forms--Certificates (Box 177)
    General note
    Certificate of Recognition
  - Family Health - 4-H Health Series, undated; cuid1660; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - First Aid and Home Nursing: A 4-H Teenagers Health Series, undated; cuid1661; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Food Guide, 1994-2001; cuid1662 (Box 191)
  - Foods and Traditions - 4-H Series, undated; cuid1663; 1 Items (Box 179)
  - 4-H, 2002-2008; cuid1697 (Box 235)
  - 4-H Activity Sheets on Foods and Nutrition, undated; cuid1574; 1 Items (Box 177)
  - 4-H Camp, undated; cuid1575; 1 Items (Box 109)
  - 4-H Chemical Use Record - Dairy Animals, Livestock, Poultry, and Animal Housing (Pesticides, Feed Additives, and Drugs), undated; cuid1576; 1 Items (Box 179)
  - 4-H Clothing and Textiles Series, undated; cuid1577; 1 Items (Box 177)
  - 4-H Club, 1955-1957; cuid1578; 1 Items (Box 115)
  - 4-H Club Enrollment, 1958; cuid1579 (Box 185)
  - 4-H Club Enrollment, 1959; cuid1580 (Box 185)
  - 4-H Club Enrollment, 1959; cuid1581 (Box 189)
  - 4-H Club Enrollment, 1960; cuid1582 (Box 189)
  - 4-H Club Enrollment, 1962; cuid1583 (Box 187)
  - 4-H Club Enrollment, 1964; cuid1584 (Box 189)
  - 4-H Club Enrollment, 1965; cuid1585 (Box 189)
  - 4-H Club Enrollment, 1966; cuid1586 (Box 188)
  - 4-H Club Enrollment, 1967; cuid1587 (Box 185)
  - 4-H Club Enrollment, 1970; cuid1588 (Box 190)
  - 4-H Club Enrollment, 1971; cuid1589 (Box 184)
  - 4-H Club Enrollment, 1972; cuid1590 (Box 189)
  - 4-H Club Enrollment, 1973; cuid1591 (Box 189)
  - 4-H Club Enrollment, 1978; cuid1592 (Box 184)
  - 4-H Club Enrollment, 1979; cuid1593 (Box 190)
  - 4-H Club Enrollment, 1981; cuid1594 (Box 184)
  - 4-H Club Enrollment, 1983; cuid1595 (Box 190)
  - 4-H Club Enrollment, 1985; cuid1596 (Box 190)
  - 4-H Club Enrollment, 1990; cuid1597 (Box 186)
  - 4-H Club Enrollment, 1935-1945; cuid1598 (Box 184)
  - 4-H Club Enrollment, 1935-1960; cuid1599 (Box 185)
  - 4-H Club Enrollment, 1951-1955; cuid1600 (Box 184)
  - 4-H Club Enrollment, 1955-1958; cuid1601 (Box 190)
  - 4-H Club Enrollment, 1960-1961; cuid1602 (Box 187)
  - 4-H Club Enrollment, 1961-1963; cuid1603 (Box 189)
  - 4-H Club Enrollment, 1962-1963; cuid1604 (Box 187)
  - 4-H Club Enrollment, 1965-1970; cuid1605 (Box 187)
  - 4-H Club Enrollment, 1967-1968; cuid1606 (Box 184)
  - 4-H Club Enrollment, 1970-1975; cuid1607 (Box 184)
  - 4-H Club Enrollment, 1971-1973; cuid1608 (Box 187)
  - 4-H Club Enrollment, 1974-1976; cuid1609 (Box 186)
  - 4-H Club Enrollment, 1975-1978; cuid1610 (Box 190)
  - 4-H Club Enrollment, 1978-1986; cuid1611 (Box 186)
  - 4-H Club Enrollment, 1979-1980; cuid1612 (Box 188)
  - 4-H Club Enrollment, 1980-1982; cuid1613 (Box 190)
  - 4-H Club Enrollment, 1982-1985; cuid1614 (Box 190)
  - 4-H Club Enrollment, 1986-1989; cuid1615 (Box 187)
  - 4-H Club Entomology, undated; cuid1616; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - 4-H Club Leaders, 1961; cuid1617 (Box 187)
  - 4-H Club Leaders, 1969; cuid1618 (Box 188)
  - 4-H Club Leaders, 1970; cuid1619 (Box 190)
  - 4-H Club Leaders, 1971; cuid1620 (Box 189)
  - 4-H Club Leaders, 1972-1974; cuid1621 (Box 190)
  - 4-H Club Leaders, 1981-1982; cuid1622 (Box 190)
  - 4-H Club Record Books (Units 1-3), undated; cuid1623; 1 Items (Box 177)
  - 4-H Club Record Books on Potatoes and Beekeeping, undated; cuid1624; 1 Items (Box 177)
  - 4-H Club Secretary's Book, undated; cuid1625; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - 4-H Club Treasurer's Book, 1972-1974; cuid1626 (Box 185)
  - 4-H Clubs, undated; cuid1627; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - 4-H Crafts Caravan: An Adventure in Discovery, undated; cuid1628; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - 4-H Electric Guide Series, undated; cuid1629; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - 4-H Energy Program, undated; cuid1630; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - 4-H Foods and Nutrition Free-Lance Series - Leader's Guide and Member's Guides #1-4, undated; cuid1631; 1 Items (Box 179)
  - 4-H Foods and Nutrition Project Special Series, undated; cuid1632; 1 Items (Box 177)
  - 4-H Foods and Nutrition Project Special Series, undated; cuid1633; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - 4-H Forestry Club Record Book - Tree Planting, undated; cuid1634; 1 Items (Box 177)
  - 4-H Health Series, undated; cuid1635; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - 4-H Insect Club Book, undated; cuid1636; 2 Items (Box 177)
  - 4-H is for Everyone, undated; cuid1637; 1 Items (Box 177)
    Ag Letter
  - 4-H Leader Training Series - Number II, undated; cuid1638; 1 Items (Box 179)
  - 4-H Leaders, 1971; cuid1639 (Box 184)
  - 4-H Pathways to the Future - Pennsylvania 4-H Leader Forum, 1982; cuid1640; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - 4-H Photo Fun Club, undated; cuid1641; 1 Items; Textual--Leaflets (Box 179)
  - 4-H Poultry Egg Project, undated; cuid1642; 1 Items (Box 179)
  - 4-H Rocketry Project Guide, undated; cuid1643; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - 4-H Swine Feeding Project, undated; cuid1644; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - 4-H Swine Handbook, undated; cuid1645; 1 Items (Box 177)
  - 4-H Swine Handbook, undated; cuid1646; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - 4-H Swine Project, undated; cuid1647; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - 4-H Textile Science Series, undated; cuid1648; 1 Items (Box 177)
  - 4-H TV Science Club Guide, undated; cuid1649; 1 Items (Box 179)
  - 4-H Wildlife Conservation Program, undated; cuid1650; 1 Items (Box 177)
  - 4-H You Two Program, undated; cuid1651; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - 4-H Youth Program Development, undated; cuid1652; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Idaho Centennial, 2012 (Box 283)
  - If It Is To Be…It Is Up To Me! - Pennsylvania 4-H Leaders Forum, 1986; cuid1664; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Leader's Guide, undated; cuid1665 (Box 191)
  - Leadership Skill Development, undated; cuid1666 (Box 191)
  - Let's Collect… - 4-H Series, undated; cuid1667; 1 Items (Box 179)
  - Let's Learn to… - 4-H Series, undated; cuid1668; 1 Items (Box 179)
  - Let's Make… - 4-H Series, undated; cuid1669; 1 Items (Box 179)
  - Let's Sew - 4-H Series, undated; cuid1670; 1 Items (Box 179)
  - Member's Guide, undated; cuid1671 (Box 191)
  - My 4-H Planning and Activity Guide, undated; cuid1672; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - NACAA 4-H Talent Revue, 1997; cuid1673; 1 Items (Box 191)
  - NACAA PA Presents: Duane Duncan, cuid1674; 1 Items (Box 191)
  - National 4-H Centennial Programs of Excellence, 2002 (Box 283)
  - National 4-H Club Camp, 25 Leadership Award (photograph), June 1950 (Box 283)
  - National 4-H Club scrapbook, 1940 (Box 283)
  - National 4-H Council Programs and Services, 1981 (Box 283)
  - National 4-H Talent Revue, 1985; cuid1675 (Box 191)
  - National Conference for Less-Than-Baccalaureate Degree Programs in Agriculture, 1968/10; cuid1676; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Newspaper Clipping: Paul Reber, 1983; cuid1677; 1 Items (Box 191)
  - Pennsylvania 4-H, 1975; cuid1678; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Pennsylvania 4-H Centenial: Article, August 2012 (Box 283)
  - Pennsylvania 4-H Centennial: Bulter County, Anniversary Dinner, 2012 (Box 283)
  - Pennsylvania 4-H Centennial: Centre County Proclamation, 2012 (Box 283)
  - Pennsylvania 4-H Centennial: Crawford County, 2012 (Box 283)
  - Pennsylvania 4-H Centennial: Huntingdon County, 2012 (Box 283)
  - Pennsylvania 4-H Centennial: Indiana County, 2012 (Box 283)
  - Pennsylvania 4-H Centennial: Lackawanna County (newsletters), 2012 (Box 283)
  - Pennsylvania 4-H Centennial: Leaders Forum, 2012 (Box 283)
  - Pennsylvania 4-H Centennial: NE Counties (Carbon, Schuylkill, Lehigh, Monroe, Northampton), 2012 (Box 283)
  - Pennsylvania 4-H Centennial: Montgomery County (Annual Report), 2012 (Box 283)
  - Pennsylvania 4-H Centennial: Rural Beginnings, Global Success, 2012 (Box 283)
  - Pennsylvania 4-H Centennial: Somerset County, 2013 (Box 283)
  - Pennsylvania 4-H Centennial: Wayne County, 2012 (Box 283)
  - Pennsylvania 4-H Centennial: Westmoreland County (Corn maze), 2012 (Box 283)
  - Pennsylvania 4-H Centennial: Westmoreland County (Tribune), 2013 (Box 283)
  - Pennsylvania 4-H Centennial: York County, 2012 (Box 283)
  - Pennsylvania 4-H Congress - Serving and Caring, 1971/06; cuid1679; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Pennsylvania 4-H Member's Record, undated; cuid1680; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Pennsylvania 4-H Member's Record Sheet, undated; cuid1681; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Pennsylvania 4-H Programs - Laboratories for Citizenship Develop Representatives for Democracy, undated; cuid1682; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Pennsylvania Association of Extension 4-H Agents Annual Report, 1990; cuid1683; 1 Items (Box 191)
  - Pennsylvania Friends of 4-H Annual Reports, 1981-1983; cuid1684; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Plan and Plant for Beauty Series - 4-H Leader's Handbook and Projects I-V, undated; cuid1685; 1 Items (Box 179)
  - Plantaria Series - 4-H Plant Culture and Crafts #1,3,6-12, undated; cuid1686; 1 Items (Box 179)
  - Regional Program Team 4-H, 2003-2008; cuid1698 (Box 236)
  - Regional Program Team FCS, 2004-2008; cuid1699 (Box 236)
  - Rent Event - Member's and Leader's Guides, undated; cuid1687 (Box 191)
  - Service for Victory scrapbook, 1942 (Box 283)
  - Sourcebook, 1999; cuid1688 (Box 191)
  - State 4-H Achievement Festival, 1974/08; cuid1689; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Strengthen Your Family - 4-H Series, undated; cuid1690; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Textile Science Project Guides, undated; cuid1691 (Box 191)
  - There's a Place for Adults in 4-H, undated; cuid1692; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Volunteers for the Future, 4-H Middle Management, Idaho, undated (Box 283)
  - Volunteers for the Future: 4-H Middle Management, Virginia, undated (Box 283)
  - Volunteers for the Future: 4-H Teen Leadership Development, Nebraska, undated (Box 283)
  - Volunteers for the Future: A Trainer's Guide, undated (Box 283)
  - Volunteers for the Future: After School Programs - 4-H Project Leaders' Community Improvement Projects, undated (Box 283)
  - Volunteers for the Future: Boards, Councils and Committees, undated (Box 283)
  - Volunteers for the Future: Boards, Councils and Committees, Washington State, undated (Box 283)
  - Volunteers for the Future: Building Strong Councils, Boards and Committees, Indiana, undated (Box 283)
  - Volunteers for the Future: Building Volunteers 4-H Support Groups, West Virginia, undated (Box 283)
  - Volunteers for the Future: County 4-H Councils, Kentucky, undated (Box 283)
  - Volunteers for the Future: County 4-H Councils, Oregon, undated (Box 283)
  - Volunteers for the Future: Developing Effective Area Advisory Councils, Alaska, undated (Box 283)
  - Volunteers for the Future: Developing Staff to Use Volunteers Effectively, Wisconsin, undated (Box 283)
  - Volunteers for the Future: Extension Advisory Councils and Committees, South Carolina, undated (Box 283)
  - Volunteers for the Future: Guide to Managing the County 4-H Program, Texas, undated (Box 283)
  - Volunteers for the Future: Introduction and Trainer's Guide, undated (Box 283)
  - Volunteers for the Future: Iowa, undated (Box 283)
  - Volunteers for the Future: Maine, undated (Box 283)
  - Volunteers for the Future: Middle Management, undated (Box 283)
  - Volunteers for the Future: Middle Management, Georgia, undated (Box 283)
  - Volunteers for the Future: Middle Management, Montana, undated (Box 283)
  - Volunteers for the Future: Middle Management, New York, undated (Box 283)
  - Volunteers for the Future: Middle Management, Virginia, undated (Box 283)
  - Volunteers for the Future: Middle Management Guide, Nebraska, undated (Box 283)
  - Volunteers for the Future: Project Activity Chairmen, undated (Box 283)
  - Volunteers for the Future: Replication Project, undated (Box 283)
  - Volunteers for the Future: Teens Reaching Youth, Delaware, undated (Box 283)
  - Volunteers for the Future: Teens Reaching Youth, Montana, undated (Box 283)
  - Volunteers for the Future: Trainer's Guide, undated (Box 283)
  - Volunteers for the Future: Volunteers Middle Management, Indiana, undated (Box 283)
  - Volunteers for the Future: Volunteer Middle Management, New England, undated (Box 283)
  - Volunteers for the Future: Volunteers as Resources, undated (Box 283)
  - Volunteers for the Future: Y.E.A., undated (Box 283)
  - Volunteers for the Future: Youth Volunteers in Motion, Colorado, undated (Box 283)
  - Volunteers for the Future: Youth Volunteers in Motion, Wisconsin, undated (Box 283)
  - Volunteers Recognition, 101 Ways, undated (Box 283)
  - Welcome to the 4-H Family, undated; cuid1693; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)